It happened because of the Coronavirus, which caused the global
economy to collapse and the
same situation is in India as well, this is not hidden from anyone,
but you know that whenever there is a
chemical dot and a smart
investor starts doing Dada Vibrant Lever at this time
and starts investing by following the
edit along with this study for a long-term
and making huge profits
because when something is in the dot poll
in the market, then there is a Dada chance of it rising to the same extent,
provided in such a situation you keep
watching everything comfortably and when you feel that
I am going to be launched here, then
transfer your unit from there to another page, so
today we have brought this plan for you
where you get complete freedom to see, you will be
able to change your style whenever you want, you will be able to transfer your
unit from one point to another account
and there is not going to be any extra button on
you, so if you have any
question at all about the idea and you are
going to do these in the market and you want
risk cover as well, then listen to today's video.  Watch till the end, do
not skip the search at all because I
will check the details with you, complete information of ICICI Venture's
Signature Unit Linked Plan, be it
its full criteria, benefits or terms and conditions, so
always watch the video till the end and if you are
new or love the channel for the first time, then subscribe to the channel and
definitely click on balance because
we always bring information as per the queries of our viewers,
I
am your friend Amit Raj Sharma, I warmly
welcome you all to my
beloved channel, then the name of
this plan is s02 600 plan,
which is chilli and teen age, that is 13 years
275, this plan is available in two variants, one is
normal and the other is full line, if you
buy it online, then to
know the term of the plan there, you will have to open your hair,
from 99 you will get to know the
policy term of plan, the minimum term is 13 years and the maximum term is 275  The
policy term is of Rs. 6000 if
you take a loan online,
which is the minimum premium bracket here.
If you take this plan in normal form, then the
minimum
premium is Rs. 3000 annually. The maximum amount that you will be able to pay is as per the
rules and regulations of this policy. If we
talk about
spoon dry ginger, then
you will get cover for seven times the minimum job premium that you are paying. You can get cover for the maximum premium you are paying,
but you can also increase your coverage,
I will tell you about that later.
Talking about modem premium, it is clearly done
and you get to see the mode of premium of the group.
Inside this plan, the
premium paying term comes here.
If you
take a plan for more, then there is a lower
premium paying term and there is also a regular mode of
premium that you want to pay on a regular basis.
You can choose the premium till the time of your plan.
Apart from that, if you take the option on limit,
normal.  For the plan, there was a hole, that is why we do
not go for a limited term, when we go for
238, then the option that you will get to
see there is for limited premium,
that is for five B.Ed and ten years, in
this plan you get chilli and taxi
and whatever you spend on premium,
you get relaxation under section 80C, if we
talk about parcel
withdrawal, then that
facility is also available to you in Islam, by the way, this is the
backbone of the five years for withdrawal within the unit linked plan, after 5 minutes
we
can withdraw up to 8% of our fund value, the same thing
is paid and if the
policy is taken for a minor, then it should be for 13 years at
least, only then you can withdraw,
no, it
is implemented here, along with this,
in this plan you get to see another option,
we say, you
also get to see the option of systematic parcel withdrawal,
meaning you can decide while taking the policy whether
you want to withdraw your fund value
because maximum 20%
Like Club is what percentage you can withdraw on the 1st
or 15th of the month on a
quarterly basis on your lips or on a
clearly basis. If you want a return or
want a parcel withdrawal in installments,
that option is also available to you through
systematic withdrawal options. Along with
this plan, a
company also helps you
in increasing your dividend and the name of the plan is
Wealth Booster. Now the Health Booster gets
activated as soon as the term of your policy is completed. How will it work?
We all know that there are four quarters in a year
and the performance of all four quarters is
different, so an
average of that will be calculated. If you are doing a fund investment or a
fast, but if you are doing this for a long time, then
also four quarters will come and in this year
an average of that will be calculated.
3.25 percent of its total fund value will be added
to your unit front, so the meaning of one word will
increase further. In this way, the couple
also helps you here. Not only this, the
administrative cost of this plan policy  And along with that,
you also get the returns of the commodity charges
on completion of the plan term and along with that you have the
freedom that you can increase or decrease your amount whenever you want, you can
increase it towards the plan, suppose you have
included the plan in the minimum amount, if you
want to increase it then you can increase it,
if you want to increase your premium then
you can do that too, but
you can increase the premium investment only to the extent of
your basic premium
and this option which I told you to
increase the premium and make changes,
this is called a step, if you increase the top-up
premium then your
premium of Rs. 2 will also be deducted one spoon dry ginger and the
risk cover will also increase,
how, the top-up premium you paid will be
multiplied by 1.25, so the
amount which will be formed comes, then the
risk cover will also be done inside this plan,
so here you get to see more flexibility,
now let's talk about
death benefit, if we talk about death benefit, then
we  You have 3 options to look at, so the
total unit fund value, which is
105 percent of the total premium paid
or whatever our society is, or if
we had added a top-up premium with it, meaning it
increased, then
whatever you think is higher among these three,
our nominee will get it. Now let's talk about
maturity, chilli and dipper, it is very
simple, that is, whatever the total fund value will be, you will get it at
that time, plus
you have the option to take out on the structure, this is
also called settlement. Now
this straight away
settlement option, how will it be, like
if you have turned
off the option, then when the
scooter is matured, you will get the first installment at the same time,
like what will happen to your complete nearest, you
can play the installment in the next 15 years,
you can take pimples or pimples on a monthly basis or quarterly basis.
Along with this, you also have the option
that if you have turned off the option,
after that you want a partner  It is
not necessary to
wait for 5 years for the settlement to happen. You can settle it and
take the entire fund value. However, if this
option becomes Option A, then you will
get the remaining total unit fund value.
Normally, you will
get up to 105 percent of the premium you paid,
whichever is higher. Now, let's
talk about investment options. We
all know that unit-linked products are of the
chart type. We get
growth funds, balance funds,
mutual funds, and daily points. We
invest in these. Now, different companies
create different combos and
design products differently, so that
if someone is new and has
no idea and has started investing, then if I try
our product, I can
teach myself, move forward, and get into the
habit of tracking the market and use their product. So,
here you will find four types of
settings. Number one, number two,
which I liked, number three, and
number four, number 3 comes. Our first
portfolio strategy. Now, the trick
support for your studies is the same.
You get all the options that you
invest in by looking at your skin. Okay,
and if you choose this pick polish edit,
you can use your
unit front unlimitedly.
Suppose you choose a front inside another unit swan
and you were investing in this front. Now
suddenly, because you are checking the
lead, you notice the market
's upgrade and you feel that the don is going to happen here, then you will
give another option and
there you shift the unit to the other side also towards the point. So, you
can do this unlimited times inside the g. At the same time, if
you feel that the tree-plant strategy is
not right, if you feel like this, then you can
change the object four times within a year. There is no
extra cost,
nor switch. Go to Tarzan right edit changes
and the port number is on your life
cycle.
You can also select the correct deposit of your portfolio. So,
I liked these two things here
and as I told you, Bloody Mary
in lawlessness.  If I don't have any idea, what kind of plan do I
need that allows us to make changes here and there,
alarms us, and charges us for making
those changes. This product does this,
and if you're a newcomer with absolutely no
idea, you
can start with this plan blindly, with long-term
study. The market is down, and
if you keep checking your knowledge daily,
print Ginger Friday, start reading about them,
start watching, like, then
100% you will become a better person. If you
invest like this for yourself, you will become an athlete. If
we go into the nature of this traffic plan and right now the mafia don is on the side effects of tennis, then 100% benefit can be achieved
completely. Rest Bhushan Pandey,
subject of address, we all know
that whatever we invest in, we have to
decide ourselves. We are here, so along with this,
we get to
see other options within this plan, such as the
option of premium redirection,
premium allocation,
no time charge at all within this plan, and along with that,
which  Fund management is 4G, that is
0.75 percent for the money market fund
and 1.3 percent for all other funds. The
premium administrative charges are
your 100 rupees per month
according to the strike. So these are some details of the plan
that I wanted to share with you.
If you start the policy in a country, there are
charges for that too, the
details of which are above your skin. By the way, in such a
product where we have complete freedom,
I do not think that discontinuing the policy is a matter of that. But it is your
right to know whether the Continuity 4 is there or
not, hence it is my duty to
tell you. Apart from this, there is other
information which you must read before buying this product.
For that,
I have given the link of their website in the comment section
where you can visit and
cross-check all the details. I
know that you are going to like the product. If you
like the video, you can share it
with other people. I am leaving and I take leave from
you, but before leaving, I would definitely like to remind you that
insurance protection is
never incomplete.  If it keeps happening then I will
meet you in a video, till then
stay happy, keep smiling and take
care of yourself because you are very
precious.